<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>More info. about me on Saikat Bera</title><link>http://example.org/know_me/</link><description>Recent content in More info. about me on Saikat Bera</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/know_me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awards and Achievements</title><link>http://example.org/know_me/awachi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know_me/awachi/</guid><description>Innovation in Science Pursuit for Inspired Research (INSPIRE), 2019 - 2022> Innovation in Science Pursuit for Inspired Research (INSPIRE), 2019 - 2022 Issued by Department of Science and Technology, Government of India.</description></item><item><title>Key Courses</title><link>http://example.org/know_me/keycourses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know_me/keycourses/</guid><description>Postgraduate:> Postgraduate: Linear Algebra and its Applications Data Mining and Machine Learning Design and Analysis of Algorithms Distributed Computing and Big Data Mathematical Methods – Analysis Probability and Statistics with R Programming and Data Structures with Python Visualization (with R) RDBMS and SQL Undergraduate:> Undergraduate: Probability and Probability Distributions Linear Models Statistical Inference Econometrics Regression Analysis Survey Sampling Statistical Quality Control Time Series Analysis Stochastic Processes Operational Research (OR) Real Analysis Metric Space Linear Algebra Design of Experiments Online Courses ( DeepLearning.</description></item><item><title>Positions of Responsibility</title><link>http://example.org/know_me/por/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know_me/por/</guid><description>PREDICT Presidency University Statistics Society:> PREDICT Presidency University Statistics Society: Social Media Manager, PR Team> Social Media Manager, PR Team – Tried to promote a statistical community to help each other grow, develop and enrich ourselves collectively.</description></item><item><title>Skills</title><link>http://example.org/know_me/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know_me/skills/</guid><description>Technical/Programming Skills> Technical/Programming Skills Python (Pandas, NumPy, TensorFlow etc.) R (ggplot2, Shiny) SQL (MySQL) Miscellaneous> Miscellaneous LATEX (Overleaf/R Markdown) Tableau, Power BI Microsoft Office (Excel and PowerPoint) Git</description></item></channel></rss>