<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My Description on Saikat Bera</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content in My Description on Saikat Bera</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awards and Achievements</title><link>http://example.org/know-me/awachi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know-me/awachi/</guid><description>Innovation in Science Pursuit for Inspired Research (INSPIRE), 2019 - 2022> Innovation in Science Pursuit for Inspired Research (INSPIRE), 2019 - 2022 Issued by Department of Science and Technology, Government of India.</description></item><item><title>Key Courses</title><link>http://example.org/know-me/keycourses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know-me/keycourses/</guid><description>Postgraduate:> Postgraduate: Linear Algebra and its Applications Data Mining and Machine Learning Design and Analysis of Algorithms Distributed Computing and Big Data Mathematical Methods – Analysis Probability and Statistics with R Programming and Data Structures with Python Visualization (with R) RDBMS and SQL Undergraduate:> Undergraduate: Probability and Probability Distributions Linear Models Statistical Inference Econometrics Regression Analysis Survey Sampling Statistical Quality Control Time Series Analysis Stochastic Processes Operational Research (OR) Real Analysis Metric Space Linear Algebra Design of Experiments Online Courses (DeepLearning.</description></item><item><title>Positions of Responsibility</title><link>http://example.org/know-me/por/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know-me/por/</guid><description>PREDICT Presidency University Statistics Society:> PREDICT Presidency University Statistics Society: Social Media Manager, PR Team> Social Media Manager, PR Team – Tried to promote a statistical community to help each other grow, develop and enrich ourselves collectively.</description></item><item><title>Skills</title><link>http://example.org/know-me/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:55:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/know-me/skills/</guid><description>Technical/Programming Skills> Technical/Programming Skills Python (Pandas, NumPy, TensorFlow etc.), R (ggplot2, Shiny), SQL.
Miscellaneous> Miscellaneous LATEX(Overleaf/R Markdown), Tableau, Power BI, Microsoft Office(Excel and PowerPoint), Git.</description></item><item><title>Contact Me :smile:</title><link>http://example.org/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/contact/</guid><description>You can reach out to me via mail at saikatb@cmi.ac.in and/or saikatbera2001@gmail.com. Feel free to connect with me on LinkedIn.</description></item><item><title>Exploratory Data Analysis on different data sets in R</title><link>http://example.org/projects/eda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/eda/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve done these exploratory data analysis using R while pursuing my B.Sc. Statistics degree from Presidency University, Kolkata in forms of assignments under our Professor Dr. Atanu Kumar Ghosh. I have broken down these assignment done over the years into 6 reports for easier read. Please check them out:-&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Chicago&lt;/li>
&lt;li>econ&lt;/li>
&lt;li>autompg&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Abalone&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SENIC&lt;/li>
&lt;li>birthwt&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Image Classification with Artificial Newral Network and Convolutional Neural Network using MNIST and Fashion MNIST Data Set</title><link>http://example.org/projects/mnist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/mnist/</guid><description>&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MNIST_database" target="_blank">
The MNIST database&lt;/a> (Modified National Institute of Standards and Technology database) is a large database of handwritten digits that is commonly used as a first test for new classification algorithms. We follow this tradition to investigate the performance of &lt;em>Artificial Neural Networks&lt;/em> of different complexity on MNIST. However, since MNIST is too easy for accessing the full power of modern machine learning algorithms (&lt;em>Convolutional Neural Network&lt;/em>) we will extend our analysis to the recently introduced, harder &lt;a href="https://github.com/zalandoresearch/fashion-mnist" target="_blank">
Fashion-MNIST dataset&lt;/a>.</description></item><item><title>Profile</title><link>http://example.org/posts/profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/profile/</guid><description>I did my bachelor’s in statistics and am currently pursuing my master’s degree from CMI. I enjoy solving interesting problems and developing innovative solutions. I have a strong willingness to learn, analyze and execute strategies, construct quantitative models, and conduct statistical analysis to develop innovative solutions.</description></item><item><title>Resume/CV</title><link>http://example.org/footer/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/footer/resume/</guid><description>See my resume here.> See my resume here. #</description></item><item><title>Shiny Dashboard using World Happiness and Corruption 2015-2020 Dataset</title><link>http://example.org/projects/whac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/whac/</guid><description>This is a Shiny Dashboard on the World Happiness and Corruption (2015-2020) data set, which I made for my DG1107: Visualisation course under my professor, Dr. Sourish Das, during the 1st semester of my M.Sc. in Data Science at the Chennai Mathematical Institute</description></item><item><title>Time Series Analysis of TCS Stock Prices from 2002 to 2021</title><link>http://example.org/projects/tsatcs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/projects/tsatcs/</guid><description>I have performed a time series analysis of the stock prices of Tata Consultancy Services from 2002 to 2021. I have started by visualising the data. And then I fitted models like &lt;em>&lt;strong>an autoregressive integrated moving average (ARIMA) model, Vector autoregression (VAR), SARIMA (seasonal ARIMA) model, Unobserved components model (UCM), and Dynamic Factor models&lt;/strong>&lt;/em></description></item></channel></rss>